Guide to the Howard Seifert Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- General Files, Part 2
  - AA 100: Introduction to Aeronautics and Astronautics
    - A Brief Outline of the History of Aeronautics (E. G. Reid, 1960) (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Lecture Notes on Rocket Propulsion, 1967; AA 100 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Manuscript Entitled Aeronautics and Astronautics in Six Chapters by N. J. Hoff, Copyright 1968-69 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Engineering 121: Solar Energy Utilization
    - Problems and Solutions, 1974-76 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Quizzes and Take-Home Final, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Lecture Schedule, Fall 1976 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Bibliography (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Class Grades, Fall 1975 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Lecture Notes (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Handouts, Fall 1975 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Article: Revere Solar Energy Collector (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - AA 101 Summer Course: Solar Energy Utilization
    - Lecture Schedule, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Lecture Schedule, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Handouts (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Student Reports (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Student Reports, Miscellaneous Source Articles (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Class Grades, 1975, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Bibliography (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Engineering 121 (Continued)
    - Lecture and Research Presentation Schedules (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Student Research Papers (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Student Research Papers and Miscellaneous Source Articles (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Articles (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Reference List and Suggestions for Research Topics (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Class Grades, 1974, 1975, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Lab Data (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Photovoltaic References (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Talks on Solar Energy, 1974-75 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Workshop: Solar Energy Applications, Summer 1976 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Notes and Agendas for Conferences on Energy Resources: University of Missouri-Rolla, 1974 and University of Miami (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Solar Energy for Earth Task Force Material (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Material on Metal Hydrides as a Hydrogen Fuel Source (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - International Astronautical Federation (IAF) Meeting 1976: Agenda and Selected Papers (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - AIAA Conference Papers:, 1973, 1974, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript: Advanced Solid-Propellant Rocket Engineering by R. D. Geckler (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Manuscript: Liquid Propellant Rockets, by I. Glassman (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - AIAA Subject and Author Indexes, 1968-74 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - AA 280 Course: Rocket Propulsion
    - Class Roster and Lecture Notes on Hybrid Rocket, (1962) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Quizzes and Exams, Fall 1960 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Problems and Handouts (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Article on Space Shuttle Design (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Course Notes and Lecture Schedule, 1972-73 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - AE 281 B,C Thermal Jets - Class Notes and Exams, 1947-48: (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - JPL Technical Reports: (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - An Exploratory Investigation of a 1979 Mars Roving Vehicle Mission, December, 1970
    - Semiannual Progress Report: Advanced Teleoperator Systems Requirements, January 1972
    - Analytical/Experimental Definition of Man-Machine Interface Characteristics in Remotely Manned Systems, July 1972
    - Summary Report-Advanced Teleoperator/Robot Studies for Planetary Surface Roving Vehicles, July 1972
    - Science Aspects of a Remotely Contolled Mars Surface Roving Vehicle, July 1972
    - Remote Manipulator Systems, Technology Review nd Planetary Operation Requirements, July 1972
    - Problems of Previous Projects on Scientists/Machine/Operations Interfaces, July 1972
    - Remotely Manned Systems for Exploration and Operation in Space - An Overview, July 1972
    - Advanced Automation Systems for Manipulator Control Technology Survey, December 1972
  - Correspondence Regarding Sabbatical plans from Stanford University to JPL Advanced Technical Studies Office, Spring 1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript by P. T. Carroll, JPL: A Horse for Sergeant: The Rise of Case-Bonded Internal-Burning Solid Propellant Rocket Motors, December 1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Diary of Meetings and Appointments While With JPL:, 8/71 to 8/72 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - General Brochures about JPL (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Notes from JPL Service, 7/71-8/72 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Review of JPL Teleoperator/Robot Work, June 20, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Other Teleoperator/Robot Work (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Papers on AI (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - SRI Papers on AI and Teleoperator Systems (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Summaries of JPL Projects Related to Robot Research, Manipulator Systems, AI, etc. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Third International Conference on AI, 1973 (Box 20A, Folder 20)
  - JPL Robot Research Program (Box 20A, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence while at JPL (Box 20A, Folder 22)
  - Remotely Manned Systems Symposia (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Survey of Remotely Manned Teleoperator Systems (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Teleoperators and Remote Manipulators (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - JPL Robot Research (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - JPL Manipulator Control Research (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - AIAA Electric Propulsion Technical Committee (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Solar Electric Propulsion (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Electric Propulsion Technology - Rockwell Stage (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Solar Electric Multimission Spacecraft (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - JPL Chemical Propulsion Systems (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, correspondence, notes, memoranda, proposals and other items pertaining to Solar Energy Research Institute, 1976 (Box 22)
  - Notebook of clippings, correspondence, notes, photographs, and press releases, re lunar pogo, 1968 (Box 22)
  - Notebooks of class notes and quizzes, 1960-75 (Box 22)
  - Notebooks of class notes, problems, and exams, 1947 and 1967-73 (Box 23)
  - Notebooks of class notes and problems, 1960-70 (Box 24)
  - Clippings, correspondence, reprints, proposals, reports, and brochures on classes and conferences, largely on solar energy, 1974-76 (Box 24)
  - Notebooks of class notes and problems, 1970-76 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, articles, and printed matter (Box 25)
  - Notebooks of class notes and problems, 1973-75 (Box 26)
  - GE and Westinghouse reports on solar heating and cooling of buildings, 1974 (Box 26)
  - Reports on solar heating and cooling of buildings, 1973-74 (Box 27)
  - Miscellaneous professional and personal papers, 1959-75: (Box 28)
    clippings, articles, memoranda, correspondence, biographical materials, audio tapes, memo books, and photographs; includes small reel of 16mm film of chain reaction demonstration, 1947
  - Scrapbook (possibly kept by Bucky Seifert) of clippings, and photographs from Jet Propulsion Lab, 1954 (Box 29 OS)
  - Two award certificates to Howard Seifert, 1976 (Box 29 OS)